mytokri.com 2017-12-22

# Mytokri Privacy Policy | Terms & Condition

**1. _Our Commitment_**

MyTokri commits to provide its users the safe and secure platform and guarantee their privacy and the data they share with the website. Whether you are our registered user or simply visit our website, your privacy is important to us. We recommend you to read our statement of privacy policy to comprehend what sort of personal data we obtain from users and how we utilize it.

We encourage you to share your details and get registered with us in order to provide you best quality services. In order to become our registered member, you shall provide us your name, email address, username, password and password validation. When you visit and navigate on our website, some of our services may direct you to third party web domains. Personal information shared by you with these third parties web domains will be dealt according to their privacy policy. MyTokrishall not be responsible for the information you share with these third party web domains. This privacy policy only deals with the personal information you share with us and we are not liable to protect your information provided to these third party domains. We also recommend you to be careful while sharing your personal details with third party domains. We do not guarantee, support and admit the product or information accessible at these third parties web domains, nor does a link show any connection or relation by the linked sites to MyTokri.

**2. _What information we collect from you:_**

  * **Personal information**

We only accumulate personally identifiable information that you select to share with us while registering on MyTokri. In order to provide you requested information/services or content, MyTokri may ask for personal information while registering at MyTokri. Further, we collect the email address of our valued clients who decide to communicate with us through mails for updates related to deals, offers, and discounts. Your other personal details such as gender, postal address, date of birth, feedback/suggestions, job role, occupation, views, survey information etc can be shared/provided by you on our discussion forums or other pages on our website.

You may notice that User Information (if shared) available on public domain such as forums is accessible for all users and visitors to the website. You are suggested to act cautiously before you share your personal details publicly., MyTokri doesn’t support any claim or liability of misuse of information that you share with third party or such party unfamiliar to MyTokri. We warmly welcome you to join our discussion forums to share your ideas, deals and suggestions as well as to keep you informed about our latest deals, discounts, special price offers, services and products to make your shopping experience remarkable. Until you terminate your membership with MyTokri, all data transferred by you with MyTokri in the form of penned discussion, feedback given by you, email responses, forum discussions, contents posted on our website, known property rights personified within, shall be, for all reasons, be considered as the property of MyTokri and might be authorized wholly by MyTokri for specific use.

Mytokri does not obtain your information until you knowingly share with us. In order to provide you a user-oriented online shopping platform fully equipped with user generated contents, MyTokri utilizes this information.

Mytokri does not sell, share, deal or trade in your personal information in any way apart from the manner already mentioned. We collect your personal information only to know about you (i) on forum discussion participation opportunity (ii) as participant at MyTokri (iii) to interact with you (iv)to keep you updated about our deals and offers that you might be interested in.

  * **Non-Personal Information**

Mytokri also gather several other information from you when you visit our website, including your browser type, operating system, IP address, ISP (internet service provider), and the URL of previous website you visited. This information might not be consumed to individually recognize you. This non-personal information is being used for several purposes including managing the website; troubleshoot connection issues, to collect demographic information, to determine how our visitors use our website, to estimate visitors’ frequency, duration of visit, pages navigation, association and compliance with applicable law etc.

  * **Cookies**

With the use of ‘cookies’ MyTokri automatically collects the non-personal information. Cookies are little text files that a website places on the hard drive of user’s computer to identify replicate users and assist user to use the website. Our cookies halps us to follow the consumer behaviour and collect total data to improve content, target advertising, promotional and marketing purposes.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our website. It should be noticed that MyTokri might not control the use of cookies by advertisers and third party websites. Some browsers allow users to disallow cookies, but users should note that cookies might be necessary to give several features of a website.

  * **Choice: Opt-In and Opt-Out**

The users at MyTokri have the opportunity to ‘opt-in’ to check their information consumed for the reasons not directly associated to MyTokri at the point when we ask for data. MyTokri does not give recognized data to other companies and instead, consume this data for its own purposes including but not limited to email newsletters, until the user ‘opt-in’ by selectively permitting consumption. After subscription, those users who do not want to get our notifications or newsletter may ‘opt-out’ (discontinue receiving) of such notification by answering to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or contact us. In every email we send, we give opt-out system in the text.

If personally identifiable data of users such as phone, email address, physical address, zip code etc changes or if a user does not want to obtain our services, we allow them a way to edit, change, delete, update or correct this information.

We try our best to secure user privacy; we might reveal personal information when legally required.

Sometime, we need to send urgent announcements when needed. For example, we send emails to our users in case of service suspension and website maintenance.Usually, users cannot opt-out of these notifications while they may deactivate their account. Nevertheless, these communications are not promotional in any way.

  * **Security**

Mytokri makes all possible effort to preserve the personal information revealed to the site. Conversely, MyTokri is not liable for any type of breach of security. If any user of MyTokri identifiably share personal information including email, name, or any other type of data in a forum or other public services, then he must be familiar with the fact that this information can be used by third parties. Although, while registering, a user can select whether an email is to be disclosed in profile or post of forum user. If user wants to try the referral service to tell friends about us, we may need the name or email of friends. MyTokri will automatically send the friend a one-time email to give then invitation to check our website. MyTokri saves this information for the only purpose of sending the email.

  * **Third Party Offers or Mailing Lists**

The users who subscribe to newsletters or email notifications of MyTokri will often receive mails possessing the updates about improvements and changes as well as offers of MyTokri website. This may also include exclusive promotions, products and service information or special deals (third party’s as well as MyTokri’s). This type of communications will solely come from MyTokri (as we shall never sell your email addresses) and there shall always be the choice to ‘opt-out’ of such particular broadcast emails.

  * **ATTENTION KIDS**

Children under 18 should not be allowed to put any type of information on MyTokri unless allowed by parents or guardians. MyTokri does not manage the users’ or audiences age.

Mytokri owns the rights to alter this policy anytime by posting notice of the presence of a new privacy statement. If we make decision of changing our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage and other places we believe it to be appropriate so our users stay updated about the information we collect, how we utilize it and under what situations, if any, we reveal it. We shall utilize data in association with the privacy policy under which the information was gathered.

**3. _Disclaimer_**

Mytokri does not claim to be liable or favouring the information, products or services these sites offer. We are not associated or have any union with any site linked to MyTokri in any way. All material on Mytokri is given only for the purpose of general information.

The policies and the statement summarized here are not proposed to and do not make any legal or contractual rights in or to represent any party.

## Payment Policy

  * **Terms and conditions**

MyTokri.com including our mobile app is driven by the Web Byte Technologies Pvt. Ltd. By using this website you make your agreement to the terms and conditions required by us to fulfillment of our objective within legal framework.

We may at any time without prior approval and notification to the users and we have every right to amend these terms anytime. If you want to be updated about the terms and conditions in regard to the website then please check these terms from time to time to make sure that you not leaving any points here.

We are always committed to provide you better user experience in the accessibility of this website and our website design is related to stipulated terms.

  * **Exclusion of our liability**

By inserting this section in our terms and conditions we here by believe that reading below liability exclusion will ensure you to understanding the below stated conditions are not binding us for be held any of circumstances occurred.

However nothing in this exclusion contains anything which we are required to perform as our part due to the applicable laws.

We accept that no liability arising out of the access of website including errors and website unavailability is liable on our part.

* Economic Loss
* Loss of a good reputation 
* Special, unforeseen, resulting reduction or harm,
* Suffered coming up in relationship with your use of this site and these conditions.

Access to and use of this site is at the user's own risk and we do not guarantee that the use of this site or any content downloadable from it will not cause harm to any residence, or otherwise reduce or eliminate the natural risks of the world wide web such as but not restricted to information reduction. Also, we accept no liability according of failures or loss coming up out of changes made to the information of this site by unexpected third parties.

To offer increased value to users of this site, we may offer hyperlinks to other sites or sources (that are not part of Web Byte technologies) for you to gain accessibility at your sole attention. You recognize and agree that, as you have chosen to enter the connected website we are not accountable for the provision of such exterior sites or sources, and do not review or promote and shall not be accountable or accountable, straight or ultimately, for (i) the comfort practices of such sites, (ii) the information of such sites, such as (without limitation) any marketing, content, items, products or many other components or solutions on or available from such sites or sources or (iii) the use that others kind of such sites or sources, nor for any harm, reduction or offence triggered or purported to be triggered by, or in relationship with, the use of or dependency on any such marketing, content, items, products or many other components or solutions available on such exterior sites or sources.

The above restriction or exemption may not apply to you to the extent that appropriate law may not allow the restriction or exemption of liability for unforeseen or resulting loss.

  * **Responsibility**

While we take all affordable reason and ensure that this site is kept up to date, we create no assurance or reflection that such components are accurate or reliable, or that this site will always be available, or that any problems will be fixed, or that it is free of viruses and the like. We may change the information of this site at any time without any liability. We create no reflection or assurance with regards to any third party items and solutions that you may buy through our customers. So far as permitted by law, we will not be accountable for any direct, oblique, unforeseen or resulting reduction or harm that may occur out of your accessibility, use or inability to use this site or our deal pages.

  * **Links**

In addition to the details on this site, there may be hyperlinks to third party sites, the information of which is beyond the control of us. We offer such hyperlinks to you as a convenience only. The addition of such hyperlinks is not an approval by us towards any company offering any solutions or items on any connected web page. It is under your control to exercise your own skill and proper care based to any content on those exterior sites. We will not be accountable for any reduction or harm that may occur from or relating to a connected third party web page.

  * **Rights**

We hold the IP privileges in the material of this site and all privileges are arranged. Not including any images or photography on the site, you may download, store in storage cache, display and print the information and knowledge in an unaltered form for your own or internal company purposes only provided that this observe appears with all duplicates. You must not consistently recover information or other content from this site to create or gather, straight or ultimately, a collection, or copy, re-transmit, spread or commercialize any content or details about this site, without our prior written authorization.

  * **Contact**

Questions, comments and demands regarding these conditions are accepted and you should get in touch with us.

### Stay Tuned

Stay updated with our new deals and coupons

We respect your privacy

Scroll To Top
